<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ricklab on RickLab</title><link>https://jediXL.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in Ricklab on RickLab</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>zh</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 18:04:09 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jediXL.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>My First Post</title><link>https://jediXL.github.io/posts/ricklab-now-is-open/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 18:04:09 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://jediXL.github.io/posts/ricklab-now-is-open/</guid><description>Welcome, Rick Labs is open to every interesting idea.
“The law of gravity and gravity itself did not exist before Isaac Newton.&amp;quot; &amp;hellip;and what that means is that that law of gravity exists nowhere except in people&amp;rsquo;s heads! It &amp;rsquo;s a ghost!&amp;quot; Mind has no matter or energy but they can&amp;rsquo;t escape its predominance over everything they do. Logic exists in the mind. numbers exist only in the mind. I don&amp;rsquo;t get upset when scientists say that ghosts exist in the mind.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://jediXL.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 18:31:58 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://jediXL.github.io/about/</guid><description>About We are raindrops
Different shapes, different sizes
Just meet at a strange time in our lives
Down, down, down&amp;hellip;our sound like the sea
Fly, fly, fly&amp;hellip;our sound like the cloud
Contact US: quinnw1817@ctbu.edu.cn</description></item><item><title/><link>https://jediXL.github.io/people/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 18:04:09 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://jediXL.github.io/people/</guid><description>Wang Q Wang Y Song Q Liu J Dr. Wang Quyuan Dr. Wang Quyuan research focuses on the intersection of computer science and economics in multi-agent systems. Specifically, Wang recent studies are mostly on the topics of incentive mechanisms. Wang often formulates and analyzes problems using mechanism design theory, game theory, and mathematical optimization.
Dr. Wang Ying Dr. Ying Wang received her B.S. degree in computer science from Southwest Normal University, Chongqing, China, in 2002 and her M.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://jediXL.github.io/works/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jediXL.github.io/works/</guid><description>Works Wang Q, Guo S, Liu J, et al. Profit maximization incentive mechanism for resource providers in mobile edge computing[J]. IEEE Transactions on Services Computing, 2021, 15(1): 138-149.
Wang Q, Guo S, Liu G, et al. MotiLearn: Contract-based Incentive Mechanism for Heterogeneous Edge Collaborative Training[J]. IEEE Transactions on Network Science and Engineering, 2022.
Wang Q, Guo S, Liu J, et al. MotiShare: Incentive Mechanisms for Content Providers in Heterogeneous Time-varying Edge Content Market[J].</description></item></channel></rss>